inetglobal.com 2017-12-31

# ACESSE PRIVACY POLICY

                                  ACESSE PRIVACY POLICY
Last Updated: July 19, 2016
Acesse strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an
interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your
name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy
policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party.
How we gather information from users
How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which
you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide
information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features,
such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you
participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive
areas of our site. Like most Web sites, Acesse also collects information automatically and through
the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the
name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold
information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and
password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control
the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt
additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you
can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to
accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be
asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site’s
features according to your preferences.
What we do with the information we collect
Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more
individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information
with anyone.
Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many
ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar
information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which
pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may
occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does
not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you
individually.
We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on Acesse to communicate with you
about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy;
services and products offered by Acesse and other topics we think you might find of interest.
Personally Identifiable Information collected by Acesse may also be used for other purposes,
including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce
transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you.
Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting
service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted

by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy,
merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may
be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court
order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection
with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities
whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice
prior to disclosure in such cases.
Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements
Acesse expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be
aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliate and other content
providers accessible through our site may have their own privacy and data collection policies and
practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on
a Acesse page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through
Acesse you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests
or sweepstakes offered by other parties. Acesse is not responsible for the actions or policies of
such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when
providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.
While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or
other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about
you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that
enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before.
Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use
cookies or other technology to gather information. Acesse does not control the use of this
technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or
policies of such third parties.
You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on
message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected
and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from
other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Acesse and this policy.
Children
Acesse does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about
children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information
from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you
believe Acesse has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the
address listed below.
Acesse reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically
for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will
mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will
be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.
Governing law
This policy and the use of this Site are governed by Navada law. If a dispute arises under this
Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the
following location: Clark County, Nevada. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated
with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to
submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following location: Clark County, Nevada, under
the rules of the American Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the
arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.
Acesse is controlled, operated and administered entirely within Nevada. This statement and the
policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights
in or on behalf of any party.
                      ACESSE COPYRIGHT NOTICE
1. This Copyright Notice governs the use of the web page at and its associated services, web
pages, domains and sub-domains, which are owned and operated by Acesse ("Owner").
Wherever this Notice refers to "users" it means "you", while "we" or "our" refer to Acesse and
"Web Site" refers to Acesse.com. If at any time the terms and conditions of this Copyright Notice
no longer acceptable to you, you should immediately cease use of the web site where is located.
2. You acknowledge that the web page contains information and/ or software, photographs, audio and
video clips, graphics, links and other material that are protected by copyright, trademark or other
proprietary rights
of Acesse or third parties, including but not limited to product names, logos, designs, titles, and
words or phrases which may be registered in certain jurisdictions (collectively, the "Content"). You
agree to comply with any additional copyright notices, information, or restrictions contained in any
content available on or accessed through the website. If you want to use any content of for any
reason you must obtain prior express written permission of Acesse.
3. You may not modify, publish, transmit, transfer or sell, reproduce, create derivative works from,
distribute, perform, display, or in any way exploit any of the content, in whole or in part. Content
consisting of downloadable software may not be reverse-engineered unless specifically
authorized by Acesse or the owner of the software's patent and or copyright. Subject to the
provisions of this Copyright Notice, you may post on the any content owned by you (such as your
original statements), content for which you have received express permission from Acesse and
content in the public domain. You assume all right and responsibility for determining whether any
content is in the public domain. You grant to Acesse the right to edit, copy, publish, distribute,
translate and otherwise use in any medium and for any purpose any content that you place on
without compensation to you. You represent and warrant that you are authorized to grant all
rights set forth in the preceding sentence.
4. You may not download content on that is indicated to be for sale except under the terms of the sale.
Such content is the protected and copyrightable property of Acesse. "Free" content may be
downloaded for your personal use or non-commercial distribution consistent with the terms defined in
this Copyright Notice. When using both purchased and "free" content, you will maintain and include all
copyright and other notices contained in such content. Except as expressly permitted by the copyright
laws, no copying, storage, redistribution or publication of any content is permitted without the express
permission of Acesse or the owners of such content or their authorized persons if other than Acesse.
5. We are confident that you have understood your rights and obligations in concern to the use of
and that you agree with the terms described above.
                                          Acesse Corporation
                                             5348 Vegas Dr
                                         Las Vegas, NV 89108
